Chapter 23.
Good morning," said the little prince.
"Good morning set the merchant.
This was the merchant who sold pills that had been invented to quench thirst.
You need only swallow one pill a week, and you would feel no need of anything to drink.
"Why are you selling these pills ask the little prince.
"Because they save a tremendous amount of time," said the merchant.
"Computations have been made by experts.
With these pills, you save 53 minutes in every week."
"And what do I do with 53 minutes thus saved
Anything you like..."
"As for me," said the little prince to himself,
"if I had 53 minutes time to spend as I liked,
I should walk at my leisure toward a spring of fresh water